{
    "Questions":{
        "Movies":{
            "Quiz1":{
                "Question1":{
                    "Question":"What did Smokey try to stop his car with in 'Friday'?",
                    "Answer":"His brake",
                    "Answer2":"Put the car in park",
                    "Answer3":"His foot",
                    "Answer4":"A wreck",
                    "Correct Answer":"His foot"
                },
                "Question2":{
                    "Question":"In 'Girl's Trip', who peed on the crowd on Bourbon Street? ",
                    "Answer":"Lisa and Dina",
                    "Answer2":"Dina and Sasha",
                    "Answer3":"Sasha and Ryan",
                    "Answer4":"Lisa and Ryan",
                    "Correct Answer":"Lisa and Dina"
                },
                "Question3":{
                    "Question":"Waht is the intro song in 'Belly'?",
                    "Answer":"Back To Life",
                    "Answer2":"C.R.E.A.M",
                    "Answer3":"Big Poppa",
                    "Answer4":"Me Against the World",
                    "Correct Answer":"Back to Life"
                },
                "Question4":{
                    "Question":"In what movie did Martin Lawrence get beat up by Monique?",
                    "Answer":"Big Momma's House 2",
                    "Answer2":"Death at a Funeral",
                    "Answer3":"Big Momma's House",
                    "Answer4":"Welcome Home Roscoe Jenkins",
                    "Correct Answer":"Welcome Home Roscoe Jenkins"
                },
                "Question5":{
                    "Question":"What three colors were used in the Emerald City scene in 'The Wiz'?",
                    "Answer":"Purple, Pink and Green",
                    "Answer2":"Green, Red, and Blue",
                    "Answer3":"Orange, Gold and Green",
                    "Answer4":"Green, Red and Gold",
                    "Correct Answer":"Green, Red and Gold"
                }
            }
        },
        "Music":{
            "Quiz1":{
                "Question1":{
                    "Question":"How many times did Tupac get shot?",
                    "Answer":"6",
                    "Answer2":"7",
                    "Answer3":"8",
                    "Answer4":"5",
                    "Correct Answer":"5"
                },
                "Question2":{
                    "Question":"I don't know much about algebra but I ...",
                    "Answer":"1+1 by Beyonce",
                    "Answer2":"A Change is Gonna Come by Sam Cooke",
                    "Answer3":"8",
                    "Answer4":"5",
                    "Correct Answer":"5"
                },
                "Question3":{
                    "Question":"When Kystlis says 'hands up' you should?",
                    "Answer":"Get Low",
                    "Answer2":"Back",
                    "Answer3":"Stop",
                    "Answer4":"Reverse",
                    "Correct Answer":"Get Low"
                },"Question4":{
                    "Question":"How many times did Tupac get shot?",
                    "Answer":"6",
                    "Answer2":"7",
                    "Answer3":"8",
                    "Answer4":"5",
                    "Correct Answer":"5"
                },
                "Question5":{
                    "Question":"What song did Smokey Robinson write for the Jackson 5?",
                    "Answer":"Blame It On The Boogie",
                    "Answer2":"I Want You Back",
                    "Answer3":"Who's Lovin' You",
                    "Answer4":"All I Do Is Think of You",
                    "Correct Answer":"Who's Lovin' You"
                },
                "Question6":{
                    "Question":"Who had the hishest selling album of 2004?",
                    "Answer":"Mariah Carey",
                    "Answer2":"Beyonce",
                    "Answer3":"Usher",
                    "Answer4":"Nelly",
                    "Correct Answer":"Usher"
                }
            }
        },
        "TV":{
            "Quiz1":{
                "Question1":{
                    "Question":"What",
                    "Answer":"",
                    "Answer2":"",
                    "Answer3":"",
                    "Answer4":"",
                    "Correct Answer":""
                }
            }
        }
    }

}